Your resignation letter.
你的辞职信
You are never gonna send it.
你永远不会寄出去的
I should've knowed.
我应该猜到的
I did know, really.
我其实是知道的
It's who I am.
这就是我的选择
It's not the church.
跟教堂无关
I... I love what I do because...
我爱我的工作因为
You are what you do.
你的工作就是你的身份
I wanted this.
我想要这份工作
I wanted this so much.
我太想要了
I let myself believe you when I... I knew all along.
我其实一直都知道 但我让自己相信了你
I love you.
我爱你
You love me?
你爱我
You love me, what about Grace?
你爱我 格蕾丝怎么办
I'm so sorry.
我很抱歉
The day she was born you were there.
她出生的那天你也在
I let you treat her like she was yours.
我让你像对待骨肉般得对待她
Why did I do that?
我为什么要那么做
I will always love her.
我会一直爱着她的
But you won't be there.
但你不会在我们身边了
I'm so... I'm so...
我很 我很
I'm so... I'm sorry.
我很 我很抱歉